1to1chat.net 2018-12-24

# Terms of Use and Privacy Policy

### General Terms

By calling our chat line, you agree to be legally bound by all the terms and conditions listed below and any other terms and conditions we may add in the future. If you do not agree to be legally bound by all of our terms and conditions, do not call the chat line. You agree to check this webpage often to see if we have added or deleted conditions to our terms of service.

### Language & Etiquette

You agree not use vulgar, profane, hateful, offensive or obscene language, exploit a minor in any way, use sexist, racial, homophobic, religious or sexually offensive language, discuss illegal activity, harass, threaten, embarrass, or say anything to another caller that the caller might consider offensive.

### Spam

You agree not to use the chat line to sell or promote any product or commercial enterprise (profit or non profit). You agree you will be solely responsible for what you say on the chat line. You understand there is no operator monitoring the chat line and there is no way to access any operator.

### Age

By calling the chat line you are stating you are 18 years of age or older. You understand that the chat line has no control over what is said on the chat line and is not able and does not monitor the chat line. The possibility exists that you will hear offensive, inaccurate, false or otherwise undesirable content. If a caller offends you, hang up.

### Content

You agree that the chat line "1to1Chat" and its service provider disclaims any and all responsibility or liability for the content made available through the chat line and your use of our system. You agree to hold the chat line "1to1Chat" and its service provider totally harmless and you agree to assume all risk and liability in conjunction with your use of our chat line. You agree that under no circumstances will we "1to1Chat" be held liable, in any way, for any damages resulting from the posting, distributing, or otherwise making available, communicating or transmitting any message on the chat line directly to you or to others.

### Privacy & Responsibility

We urge you to use your common sense when using the chat line. Do not reveal, or otherwise make available, any personal information, including, but not limited to, your addresses, telephone number, credit card numbers or even your last name. You understand that we do not verify the identity of chat line users and therefore you should not assume the other users “are who they say they are.”

### Usage guide

### Our Number Policy

Personal numbers are free* and can be used for a variety of uses including keeping yourself protected whilst interacting with online strangers (dating lines, chat rooms, online auctions, classifieds) offline through voice communication . By using a personal number you no longer have to give your real telephone number to people online whom you may not know well and which can expose you to safety issues. Personal numbers maybe changed free of charge* whilst your landline or mobile number maybe more difficult and costly to change .

### Acceptable use

Our personal numbers shall ONLY be used for Personal Numbering Services and PERSONAL COMMUNICATIONS. A Personal Number is defined as a Telephone Number which allow users to receive calls or other communications and have these communications forwarded to other mobile or landline numbers. Note we agree to forward your personal number to your mobile or landline in most countries. If our system does not accept your network to forward calls to please contact support@1to1chat.net.

### Unacceptable use

Please note that personal numbers should not be used in any illegal way including but not limited to:

Missed call telemarketing Outgoing call center telemarketing SMS promotional spam

Or any other commercial activity that is not in line with the original use.

We are not responsible for any complaints created by your use of our personal numbers if used incorrectly and for other purposes than outlined in this website. We reserve the right to furnish your personal data to third parties (law enforcement, etc) in the case your personal number has been reported to have been used in an abusive manner.

For other any additional question or information regarding how to use personal numbers legally please send us an email to: support@1to1chat.net

*all numbers are attributed free of charge for a period of 30 days. A minimum incoming volume of 100 minutes per month is required to keep a free personal number. We reserve the right to change your personal number at any time and replace with another similar number.

### Billing

You agree to assume responsibility for all costs for calling the chat line. You agree to check with your telephone provider to determine if calling the chat line is a local or long distance call. You understand that calling us may result in a toll charge to your phone bill and you are liable for such charges. For many people, calling the chat line is a totally free local call. For some callers, standard long distance charges may occur. Cost of calls to the UK 070 number range are 51p per minute from a BT landline within the United Kingdom only, calls from mobiles will be considerably more, have the bill payers permission.

### Caller Privacy

We do not collect any personally identifiable information about you on this website, except time of call, Date of call and telephone number. We do not share, sell, or barter any information about anyone to anyone unless under Court Order or from a request from law enforcement agency. We advise you to review this Agreement regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [support at 1to1chat dot net](mailto:support@1to1chat.net).

### Choice/Opt-out:

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at support at 1to1chat dot net or use the unsubscribe button from the e-mail received.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

At www.1to1chat.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.1to1chat.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

www.1to1chat.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adwords.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html).

### Privacy Policy

1to1chat respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to our web sites, including www.1to1chat.com (collectively, the “1to1chat Sites” or “Sites”). This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect through the Sites, how we use that information, and what choices you have. The 1to1chat Sites may contain links to other web sites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any companies or individuals that 1to1chat does not control, or any web sites that you link to from the 1to1chat Sites. You should use caution and review the privacy policies of any sites that you visit from ours to learn more about their information practices. Please take a few moments to read this agreement. By accessing the 1to1chat Sites, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future as indicated below.

### Type of data collected

In various places on the 1to1chat Sites, we may collect “Personally Identifiable Information,” such as your name, age, gender, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address or other information that can be used to contact you or identify you as an individual. For example, we collect this information when you register for our chat site From time to time in the future we may offer additional features, services, and promotional opportunities that would require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information to participate. We also collect “Anonymous Information” such as your IP address, the type of browser you use, the pages on our Sites that you have visited, and the advertisements that you have clicked on. Your Personally Identifiable Information is linked to your Anonymous Information. Like many Internet sites, we also use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer and is stored on your hard drive. When you visit our Site(s) the cookie identifies your computer to us so that you do not have to re-register each time you visit. We may also use cookies to measure the traffic to our Sites and the use of different services and features of the Sites. Advertisers that appear on the 1to1chat Sites may place cookies on your computer and their use of the information stored on those cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. You should visit their sites to learn about their information practices. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to 1to1chat’s cookies. We do not intend that children will use our sites. We do not solicit or knowingly collect information from children under 13 years old, nor will we accept registration from them.

### Use of collected information

We use Personally Identifiable Information that you provide to communicate with you, to customize advertising and content available on the 1to1chat Sites, to conduct research for internal purposes and to use such information to improve our services and the 1to1chat Sites. If you have uploaded if you so choose, we will also use it to send you information about products and services that may be of interest to you. Later on in this Privacy Policy, we provide you with more information on what choices you have. We use information that is not personally identifiable to determine how people use our web site and its services. For example this data tells us information including how often users click on our advertisements, which files are downloaded most frequently, and which areas of our site are the most popular. Analyzing this data allows us to improve the offerings on and performance of our site(s). Using your IP address, we can also determine the general physical location of a user and may at times use this information to better target advertising to users.

### Share of information

Except as noted below, 1to1chat does not share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties unless you give us your permission or we need to share such information in order to provide products or services you have requested. For example, we engage third parties to assist us by tracking the number of visitors to the Sites that have "clicked-through" from specified promotions on third party sites and those visitors' activities on the 1to1chat Site. When we supply personally identifiable information to these third parties, we require them to use it only for the function they are helping us with. When you see parts of our site with a prominent brand of another company, information you supply (or authorize for use) in that part of the site will be shared with the other company that is cooperating in providing the service. Please visit that company’s site to learn more about their information practices. We aggregate the Anonymous Information that we collect and exchange it with advertisers and others who are interested in our services. Third party vendors, including Google, Teracent, and Double Click use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information when required by law or under the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to conform to applicable law, comply with subpoenas, court orders or legal process served on 1to1chat, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, and to protect the property or interests of 1to1chat, its agents and employees, personal safety, or the public. Under such circumstances, 1to1chat may be prohibited by law, court order or other legal process from providing notice of the disclosure, and 1to1chat reserves the right to not provide such notice in its sole discretion. If we become part of another organization, including without limitation, by merger, change of control, sale of assets, or other acquisition, the acquiring organization will obtain and have access to the Personally Identifiable Information collected by 1to1chat and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personally Identifiable Information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we cease operation, your information may be transferred to and used by another company that offers similar or related products or services. While we cannot predict a great deal about such an unlikely event, we would hope this could provide you continuity of service.

### User changes to data

To delete your Personally Identifiable Information, you must unsubscribe on http://qa.ee OR send an E-Mail to support@qa.ee. Please note that the public comments made by a user in a chat room or a forum cannot be deleted. Since, Anonymous Information is not identifiable as originating with you, it cannot be reviewed or changed by you.

You may opt out of the third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting one of the following pages:

http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/

http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out/

### Publicly posted information

If you register atthe 1to1chat Sites and make postings to chat rooms, forums or your user page, please remember that anything you post is publicly available. The user name you have chosen during the registration process is visible to all users of the Site. If you visit another member’s user page, your user name will appear on that page. Your user page will also show certain statistics regarding your use of the Site, such as the date you became a member, how long ago you last visited the Site, the categories of materials you have posted. Your user profile, and the information you choose to include in your profile, will also be available to other users of our chat rooms, forums and to visitors that access your personal user page. 1to1chat does not control, and is not responsible for, the use of any information or content that you have exposed to the public through your use of the 1to1chat Sites.

### Security

We keep the Personally Identifiable Information you provide on servers that are protected by firewalls and other technological means against intrusion or unauthorized access. They are located in a physically secure facility, and only our employees and agents with a need to know the information are given access. While no amount of security can give a perfect guarantee, you can have a high degree of confidence that the personally identifiable information you give us is protected from unauthorized access and use. We rely on you to select passwords that cannot be guessed easily and to safeguard those passwords from disclosure. Please contact us if you have any information regarding unauthorized use of the 1to1chat sites.

### Updates

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our services change and expand. If we update this Privacy Policy, we will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the email address specified in your account or by posting a notice of such changes on the 1to1chat Sites. Unless otherwise provided, the revised terms will take effect on the date they are posted. Once such changes become effective, your continued use of the Site will signify your acceptance of the new Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, or any revised Privacy Policy, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Site.

### Questions

If you have questions about this Statement or our policies, please contact us at: Support at 1to1chat dot net
